{
  "minecraft-version": "バージョン",
  "plugin-load-problem": "プラグイン '{{plugin-name}}' をロードできませんでした",
  "pocketmine-version": "Pocketmineのバージョン",
  "bedrock-version": "統合版のバージョン",
  "forge-version": "Forgeのバージョン",
  "authme-shutdown-problem": "AuthMeの読み込みに失敗したので、サーバーをシャットダウンします",
  "pex-config-problem": "PermissionsExのコンフィグが間違っています。",
  "ambiguous-plugin-name-problem": "複数のバージョンの{{plugin-name}} が入っています。{{first-plugin-path}}、{{second-plugin-path}}",
  "plugin-dependency-problem": "{{plugin-name}} の前提プラグインの{{dependency-plugin-name}} を入れてください",
  "plugin-disabling-problem": "{{plugin-name}} を無効にできませんでした",
  "plugin-enabling-problem": "{{plugin-name}} を有効にできませんでした",
  "plugin-runtime-problem": "{{plugin-name}} で問題が発生しました",
  "forge-confirm-problem": "サーバーを再起動してください",
  "mod-dependency-problem": "{{mod-name}} の前提MODの{{dependency-mod-name}} が見つかりませんでした",
  "mod-dependency-problem-plural": "{{mod-name}} の前提MODの{{dependency-mod-list}} が見つかりませんでした",
  "mod-duplicate-problem": "複数のバージョンの{{mod-name}} が入っています。{{first-mod-path}}、{{second-mod-path}}",
  "mod-exception-problem": "{{mod-name}} で予期しないエラーが発生しました",
  "mod-fatal-problem": "{{mod-name}} で重大なエラーが発生しました",
  "world-missing-mod-problem": "{{mod-name}} が入っていたワールドですが、{{mod-name}} が見つかりません",
  "world-mod-version-problem": "ワールドはmod'{{mod-name}}'のバージョン{{mod-expected-version}} が入った状態で保存されており、このmodの最新バージョンは{{mod-current-version}} です。",
  "plugin-incompatible-problem": "'{{plugin-name}}'はこのサーバーのバージョンとは互換性がありません。",
  "aquatic-world-on-older-version-problem": "このワールドはバージョン1.13以降で作成または読み込まれました。この新しい形式のワールドはどの古いバージョンでも読み込むことはできません。",
  "old-player-directory-problem": "サーバーは古いプレイヤーディレクトリをセーブデータから検知しました。",
  "command-run-solution": "コマンド {{command}} を実行します。",
  "authme-shutdown-solution": "'stopServer'の値を'true'にしてください。",
  "configure-plugin": "{{plugin-name}} を設定します。",
  "configure-plugin-with-file": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}} ({{suggested-file}}).",
  "plugin-install-different-version-solution": "{{plugin-name}} の他のバージョンをインストールしましょう。",
  "plugin-install-solution": "プラグイン {{plugin-name}} をインストールします。",
  "plugin-remove-solution": "プラグイン {{plugin-name}} を削除します。",
  "file-delete-solution": "{{file-path}} のファイルを削除します。",
  "file-edit-solution": "{{file-path}} のファイルを編集します。",
  "mod-install-different-version-solution": "'{{mod-name}}' の他のバージョンをインストールしましょう。",
  "mod-install-solution": "Install the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution-with-version": "Install the mod '{{mod-name}}' with version {{mod-version}}.",
  "mod-remove-solution": "Remove the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "aquatic-version-install-solution": "Update the server software to 1.13 or newer.",
  "plugin-command-exception-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' cannot execute the command '{{command}}'.",
  "ticking-block-entity-problem": "A block in the world is causing problems.",
  "remove-block-solution": "Remove the block from the world, e.g. with MCEdit.",
  "do-nothing-solution": "Do nothing. This problem might fix itself.",
  "chunk-load-exception-problem": "There was an exception while loading the world chunks.",
  "remove-chunk-solution": "Remove the problematic chunk from the world, e.g. with MCEdit or by removing the region file.",
  "multiverse-load-problem": "The world '{{world-name}}' could not be loaded because it contains errors and is probably corrupt.",
  "world-repair-solution": "Repair the world '{{world-name}}', e.g. by using Minecraft Region Fixer or MCEdit.",
  "world-duplicate-problem": "World '{{world-name}}' is a duplicate of another world and has been prevented from loading.",
  "mod-wrong-minecraft-version-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is not compatible with the Minecraft version {{minecraft-version}}.",
  "forge-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different Forge version."
}